本字幕由 ShinY 深影字幕组 原创翻译制作
深影字幕组论坛地址 http://shinybbs.com
翻译： Virus Killer  红鼻子的UFO  Yatamisaki  Eraugus  带着猫咪私奔  熊猫大虾
校对/后期： iamazed
机器之心
第一季  第一集
2048年
科技的发展已经失去了控制
未知的毒品及武器在街道和学校泛滥
走私团伙被不明暴力犯罪组织操纵
犯罪率也惊人地提高了400%
人手不足 装备落后 执法机关只得颁布一项新的措施:
每名警察都需配备一名先进的机器战警作为搭档
我们中埋伏了
It's an ambush!
约翰 真该死
John, damn it.
我中弹了 我不行了
I've been hit! I'm down!
- 佩勒姆 - 我在西侧
- Pelham! - On the west side!
佩勒姆不行了
Pelham's down.
- 我要你带我进去 - 我们不知道里面有多少人
- I need you to lead me in! - We don't know how many suspects are in there.
- 冒生命危险去救另一... - 闭嘴
- Risking one life to save one life... - Shut up!
带我进去 快
Lead me in! Move!
嘿 兄弟 情况不太妙啊
Hey, buddy. So this ain't good.
对 确实不妙 但有些情况比这还糟糕
No, it's not. Could always be worse!
还真更糟糕了
It just got worse.
他们早就等着我们送上门了 约翰
They were ready for us, John.
反联组织怎么知道我们要来
How did Insyndicate know we were coming?
他们怎么知道的
How did they know?
- 机器人 - 他们怎么知道的
- MX! - How'd they know?
我们要撤离这里 给他诊断一下
We're getting out of here. Give me a diagnostic!
血压正在下降
Blood pressure's dropping,
腹腔动脉被炸断了
celiac artery's blown apart.
我们无能为力了 长官
There's nothing to do, sir.
我们要撤离这里
We're getting out of here.
在你带他离开之前 他就会失血过多而死
He will bleed to death before you get him out of here.
- 闭嘴 掩护我们 我们要撤了 - 我不能那么做
- Shut up! Cover us! We're leaving! - I cannot do that.
统计结果表明其余人生还的可能性更大
Others have a better statistical chance of surviving.
我需要保护他们
I need to protect them.
- 你是否要陪着你的搭档 - 我当然要
- Are you staying with your partner? - You're damn right I am!
嘿 你给我回来
Hey! Come back here!
跟我来
Come on.
告诉我你记起了什么
Tell me what you remember.
这一次...
This time...
我记起了无线电呼叫
I remember the radio call.
佩勒姆呼叫的
From Pelham.
你的搭档
Your partner.
对 但仅此而已了
Yeah. But not much more than that.
我还是想不起所有细节
I still can't remember every detail.
我想再来一次
I want to go again.
你今晚已经有很大进步了 约翰
You made good progress tonight, John.
你昏迷了十七个月 对吧
You were in a coma for 17 months, yes?
严格意义上来说 我们应该等你完全清醒一年
Technically, we shouldn't be doing this procedure
再进行这项程序
until you've been fully conscious for one year.
是啊
Yeah.
严格意义上来说
Well, technically...
你只是一个没有行医执照
you're an unlicensed doctor from SubAsia
而且私用黑市药物的亚洲医生
practicing black market medicine.
没错
Well, yes,
如果你愿意可以把我关进监狱
you can throw me in prison if you want,
但是 我是出于好意 把你当做病人收留了
but... I accepted you as a patient out of kindness.
我最初见到你的时候 你看起来很绝望
You seemed like a desperate man when I met you.
现在呢
And now?
现在 你看起来很绝望
Now... you seem like a desperate man.
约翰 我知道你说过伏击你们的人消失了
John, I know you said the people who ambushed you disappeared,
但是 就算我尽最大的努力
but, despite my best efforts,
你可能还是想不起他们是谁
you may not remember who they are.
大多数来找回忆师的人
Most people come to a Recollectionist...
是为了想起一些美好的事物
they want to remember good things.
你为什么就不能放下这件事呢 已经两年了
Why can't you let this go? It's been two years.
你要知道
You know...
他们杀了我的队友
they killed my team...
我的朋友
...my friends.
不接受这项治疗 我就想不起任何事
And without this treatment, I can't remember anything.
我这次还想起了一些别的事情
I remembered something else this time.
我的前女友
My ex-girlfriend.
安娜
Anna.
我们在我的公寓里
We were in my apartment.
奇怪了
Strange.
下次我来...
I'll, uh...
改进一下那组集群的触发器
refine the triggering of that cluster next time.
你流鼻血了
Your nose is bleeding.
警探
Detective.
你还好吗
You all right?
还好
Yeah.
你的机器人搭档呢
Where's your MX?
我下班了
I'm off duty.
- 你的人类搭档呢 - 在和目击者谈话
- Where's your human? - Talking to a witness.
一小时前有几个人翻墙过来了
Individuals came over the wall an hour ago.
请小心驾驶
Drive safely.
我会的
Yeah, I will.
738天前的信息
Message saved for 738 days.
嗨 宝贝
Hi, honey.
我知道你可能还在睡觉 但是
So, I know you're probably still asleep, but,
约翰 太阳就要落山了
John, the sun is setting
这是我见过的最美的景色
and it is the most beautiful thing I've ever seen.
快看
Look.
你爸爸肯定会喜欢这个地方
Your father would've loved this place.
哦 我等不及要回到你的身边了
Oh, I can't wait to get back to you.
我知道我还得再等一个星期 但是...
I know I have to wait a week, but...
我真的很希望你能在这里陪着我
what I really wish is that you were here with me.
- 早上好 - 早上好
- Morning. - Morning.
- 你来上班吗 - 我知道我说过我准备好了
- You coming in? - I know I said I was ready.
只要再给我一天假就好
Just give me one more day.
不 我已经给过你一天假了
No. I already gave you one more day.
然后又是一天 又是一天
And another and another.
是时候了 约翰
It's time, John.
约翰
John?
我刚刚收到一个报告 在南凯尔文发生了一起武装抢劫
I just got a report of a coordinated armed robbery in South Kelvin.
看起来像是反联组织干的
Looks like it was Insyndicate.
反联组织
Insyndicate?
好吧
Okay.
我一会就过去
I'll come in.
人造骨骼校准未完成
Synthetic calibration incomplete.
人造骨骼校准未完...
Synthetic calibration incompl...
- 我无法访问系统 你进去了吗 - 我进去了
- I can't access the system. Are you in? - I'm in.
我登陆不进去啊
I'm not in. I'm out.
我所有文件都被锁住了
All my files are locked.
听起来像是马丁内斯又在作弄你了
Sounds like Martinez is messing with you again.
我们应该在休战了
We're supposed to be in a truce,
如果是真的 我要杀了他
so, if that's true, I'm gonna kill him.
还有另一种可能性
Well, there is one other possibility.
你是不是又忘了你的密码了 沃格尔探长
Did you forget your password again, detective Vogel?
睡了两年的人看来状态不错
Not bad for a guy who's been asleep for two years.
我不敢苟同
I wouldn't say that.
我看他很弱
He looks weak, to me.
理查德
Richard,
我知道这对你来说不容易 但不要当刺头儿
I know this won't be easy for you, don't be a prick.
这个部门就算没有他也能办好事
This department's handled affairs just fine without him.
你对肯尼思有什么意见
What's your problem with Kennex?
别听他废话 你会无聊死的
Don't ask to hear the story... you'll die of boredom.
还会被浓烈的嫉妒情绪毒害
And exposure to severe envy.
他有什么可让人嫉妒的
Look, there's nothing to envy in him.
肯尼思负责的那次突击
Kennex oversaw that raid,
明明掌握了所有情报 却使他的队伍被伏击
controlled all the intel and got his team ambushed.
除了肯尼思这个负责人 所有人都被杀了
Everyone, except the one man responsible... Kennex... was killed.
他应该被免职才对
Should've been discharged.
理查德
Richard.
他不会久留
He won't last.
你们瞧好吧
You just watch.
约翰・肯尼思注册完成
Kennex, John. Registration complete.
谢谢
Thanks.
肯尼思警探
Detective Kennex,
我是编号785 我被指派给你了
I'm 785. I've been assigned to you.
我知道这是你回来的第一天
I'm aware this is your first day back.
我只想帮助你尽可能顺利的适应现役职务
I only want to make your acclimation to active duty as smooth as possible for you.
我会参与你所有...
I'm here to attend to all your n...
我不会和那种东西一起出车
I'm not driving with one of those things.
对我爸来说 有人类搭档就够了
Human partner was good enough for my father.
对我来说也一样
It's good enough for me.
自从你离开之后
Since you were last here,
配备MX已经成了硬性规定
MX partners have become mandatory.
我不想就规章制度的事跟你吵 好吗
I'm not gonna fight you on some kind of regulation thing, okay?
- 我不干 - 不干也得干
- I'm not doing it. - Like hell you're not.
你读过蒂尔登分析你的档案吗
Have you read Tilden's profile of you?
顺便说一下 他是个非常厉害的精神病医生
And, by the way, he is a very capable psychiatrist.
"肯尼思永远不能复职"
"Kennex should return to service never."
永远 这...这时间长了点吧
Never? Wow, that's... that's a long time.
"肯尼思饱受抑郁症 精神萎靡
"Kennex is suffering from depression, mental atrophy,
创伤性强迫症 创伤后应激障碍
trauma onset OCD, PTSD
以及心理上排斥仿生部件等问题的折磨"
and psychological rejection of his synthetic body parts."
最后一句倒是真的
Well, that last part is true.
听着 你是唯一一个比我更迫切地
Listen, you're the only person more desperate than I am
想知道反联组织是怎样知道那次突击的
to find out how Insyndicate learned about the raid.
只要我们合作就会找到答案
If we work together, we can do it.
案件发生在几小时前
This happened a few hours ago.
劫持目标是一辆装有生物研究制品的武装卡车
Robbery target was an armored truck, carrying bio research.
如果这起劫案是反联组织策划的
If this is an Insyndicate operation,
我们或许能更了解他们
it might help us learn more about them.
和上次行动有什么联系
What's the connection?
使用抛物线型脉冲电荷来阻止车辆
Parabolic pulse charge was used to stop the vehicle.
伏击之后我就没见过这种作案手法
I haven't seen that since the ambush.
那倒像是反联组织干的
Well, sure looks like Insyndicate.
- 库存报告在吗 - 还没有
- Inventory report? - That's not in yet.
不管他们想要什么 他们杀了四名安保人员
Whatever they wanted, they killed four security guards to get it.
其中一个劫匪被我们打伤
One of the thieves was shot.
正在郡医院接受治疗
He's being treated at County.
约翰
John?
反联组织的事不要告诉别人 好吗
Keep the Insyndicate connection between us, okay?
你觉得我们部门有内奸
You think someone in the department's working with them?
你是我唯一相信的人
You're the only guy I trust here.
好的
Okay.
我去查查
I'll check it out.
还有一件事
One more thing.
对你的搭档好一点
Go easy on your partner.
走吧
Come.
卡车是全能公司的一间私人实验室的
Truck belongs to a private lab run by Omni,
他们公司从事的是DNA研究
company specializing in DNA research.
据经理说
According to the manager,
车里是装有人造单链可编程DNA的试剂瓶
they were transporting vials of single-strand synthetic, programmable DNA.
探长 我是瓦莱丽・斯特尔
Detective? Valerie Stahl.
约翰・肯尼思
John Kennex.
- 见到你很高兴 - 我也是
- Pleasure to meet you. - You, too.
好的
Okay.
说说你对可编程DNA知道些什么
So tell me what you got on programmable DNA.
可编程DNA可以用来启动组织的再生过程
Programmable DNA can be used to trigger the process of tissue creation.
比如 可以利用人体来培育器官
For example, to grow sets of organs in humans,
再拿去贩卖
possibly for harvest.
还带走了什么东西
What else was taken?
酸 苯碳化物 塞亚诺 迈克隆红
Acid, bencarmidium, thianel, Myklon Red.
迈克隆红
Myklon Red.
迈克隆红 迈克隆红
Myklon Red, Myklon Red...
探长
Detective?
探长 你没事吧
Detective, you okay?
没事 我很好 谢谢
Yeah, I'm fine. Thanks.
这片区域是黑色高棉组织的地盘
This sector is Khmer Black territory.
高棉是柬埔寨的旧称
他们以前就是搞生物技术非法交易的
They've been known to traffic in biotech in the past.
我们正在搜捕其中有嫌疑的人
We're rounding up the usual suspects.
你觉得不是他们干的
You don't buy it?
鲁比・马半年前接替了他死去哥哥的位子
Ruby Mah assumed leadership of the gang six months ago
成了团伙的老大
when his brother was killed.
但团伙内部对此有异议 他们认为他太过西化了
It was controversial. He's seen as too Western.
所以他需要向手下展示他传统的一面
He needs to show the people he's traditional.
今天是柬埔寨新年的最后一天
Today is the last day of the Cambodian New Year,
叫做新岁日 是忏悔过错的一天
Loeung Sakk, a day of repentance for wrongdoing.
他今天不会实施暴力
He wouldn't commit violence today.
这是其他组织干的
This was another gang.
我去找找行为倾向的数据 确定犯罪模式
I'll find behavioral tendencies in data and identify criminal patterns.
还是我来之前情报分析员就已经分析过了
Or didn't intelligence analysts do that before I got here?
谢谢 我 呃...非常感谢
Thanks. I, uh... I really appreciate it.
失陪
Excuse me.
没事
Sure.
- 告诉总部我们要回去了 - 刚刚你怎么回事
- Tell command we're 10-19. - What happened back there?
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
看起来像癫痫症发作
It seemed like a petit mal seizure.
我必须向上级报告
I will need to report what I saw.
我没事 你不需要报告任何事
I'm fine. You're not gonna report anything.
昨晚你在科隆街区
You were in Koln Avenue District last night.
一个MX看到了你
An MX saw you there.
据我所知 探长
I am concerned, Detective.
那片区域有大量地下黑诊所
That area is populated by numerous black market medical clinics.
还有美味的拉面馆
And some tasty noodle joints.
听着 我很感谢你的关心
Look, I appreciate your concern,
不过没什么需要报告的
but there's nothing to report.
另一件奇怪的事 肯尼思探长
Another curious thing, Detective Kennex?
昨晚 你的呼吸中没有夹杂食物颗粒
Last night, there were no comestible trace particles on your breath,
表明你并没有吃拉面
indicating you were not there for noodles.
我认为我们应该...
I think we should...
嗨 鲁迪
Hey, Rudy.
我不是撞鬼了吧
As I live and breathe.
或者说 你居然还活着
Or should I say, as you live and breathe?
最近怎么样
How are ya?
每天都在回绝派对邀请
Constantly turning down party invitations.
现在我已经很受女性欢迎了
I've become quite popular with the ladies.
要我做什么
How can I help?
我需要一个新机器人 这是授权令
I got a rec order for another synthetic.
他摔坏了
He fell?
掉出了疾驰的汽车
Out of a moving car?
是啊 很惊讶吧 一定是软件的问题
Yeah, crazy, huh? Must be some kind of software issue.
我得搞个新的
Gonna need a new one.
软件会出问题
Software?
鉴于我们没有可用的MX机器人
Since we don't have any MXs available,
而警局允许服役的机器人只有这一款了
department's only cleared one model for active duty.
有趣的是 这个其实...
Funny, actually. This, uh...
这个下个月要被安排转移到NASA去
this unit was scheduled to be transferred to NASA next month.
NASA: 美国国家航空航天局
挺可悲的
It's sad really.
他只是坨废铁
He's scrap metal.
他脊椎里用稀土金属做成的电路
The trimidium circuits in his spinal column are
比他全身加起来都值钱
worth more than the whole of him.
等等 这是...这是疯了的那款吧
Wait a minute. That's... that's one of the crazy ones.
什么 才不是呢 这么说太粗鲁了
What? No. That's rude.
- 本质上说不算疯 - 你知道 他们有...
- Not crazy, per se. - You know, they had their...
什么 毛病 谁还没点毛病呢
What? Problems? Who doesn't have problems?
技术角度来说 他们功能完美
Technically, they're perfectly functional.
看看他
Look at him.
很适合出门
He's road-worthy.
约翰 这是多利安 多利安这是约翰
John, Dorian. Dorian, John.
好了 应该能用了
There. Should be functional.
他的测向器以前坏了
His DF was bad.
有什么我要注意的吗
Anything I need to know?
DRN系列的机器人
Well, the DRN series--
他们是基于一个叫人造灵魂的项目而开发
they were based on a program called Synthetic Soul.
按你的说法 当他不疯的时候
And while he isn't crazy, as you say,
会有一些小故障
there may be some bugs.
故障 什么样的故障
Bugs? What kind of bugs?
有一些机器人无法处理他们的情感准则
Some of them had difficulty dealing with their emotive regulations.
出现情感问题
Emotional issues.
DRN的设计初衷是让其尽可能的和人类接近
The idea behind the DRNs was to be as human as possible.
而事实上 人类会有一些无法预计的情绪反应
And the truth is that it's human to have unexpected emotional responses.
如果把接近人类作为目标的话
And if, uh, being as close to human was the goal, then,
那我想DRN系列应该不算太失败
I guess the DRNs weren't such a failure after all.
人们会情绪崩溃
People have breaking points, and...
所以DRN也会崩溃
so do DRNs.
所以你的意思是他是个不健全的人
So you're saying he's a basket case.
我可没说过 也没承认过
Not words I would use, or agree with.
好吧 准备好了就插上电源吧 我得回街上了
All right, plug it in already. I got to get back on the street.
好的
Okay.
唤醒他的荣幸就交给你了
Please have the honor of waking him up yourself.
触碰他的左耳
Touch it against his left ear.
我睡了多久
How long was I out?
四年零三个月
Uh, four years and three months.
约翰・肯尼思探长
Detective John Kennex.
我叫多利安 你好
I'm Dorian. How are you?
您的记录非常杰出
Your record is outstanding.
过去是
Used to be.
抱歉
Excuse me?
更新你的资料 我们走
Update your files. Let's go.
嘿 老大
Hey, boss.
他出来了
He's on the move.
我们走
Let's go!
大家听见了吗 我们走
You heard him. Let's go.
我该怎么称呼您
So what do I call you?
探长
Detective.
好吧 探长 这活儿可比在CNA太空站
Well, Detective, this sure beats repairing thermal insulation tiles
修补隔热砖强多了
on the C.N.A. Space Station.
你也知道 我四年前就退役了
I was decommissioned four years ago, as you know.
为什么我和你在一辆车里
Why am I in this car with you?
我必须和一个人造人一起开车
I'm required to ride with a synthetic.
我对那个词可不感冒
I'm not a huge fan of that term.
圣・克里斯托弗
St. Christopher.
这肯定是别人送你的礼物 对吗
This has to be a gift from someone. Am I right?
大约80%的可能性是件礼物
Something like 80% of these are given as gifts.
人造人都是很严谨的
Synthetics are precise.
又是那个词
There's that term again.
你刚刚说"大约80%"
You just said, "Something like 80%."
准确的数据是83.42%
The actual statistic is 83.42%,
但我在运行我的日常口语程序
but I'm running my colloquialism routine,
所以我得表达大量的口语数据 伙计
so I express most data conversationally, man.
棒极了
Terrific.
那"A"是谁
So, who's "A"?
艾迪森 安妮 艾德琳
Addison? Annie? Adeline?
阿兰娜 安尼塔
Alana? Anita?
艾米 奥黛丽 海蓝宝石
Amy? Audrey? Aquamarine?
好吧 够了 行了吗
Okay, that's enough, all right?
人造人系统关闭
Um... synthetic off.
人造人关机
Synthetic off?
你是说 让我安静吗
Does that mean you want me to be quiet?
对 不管你的安静模式是什么 调到那个模式
Yeah, whatever the mode is for you to be quiet, just do that.
哥们 我能安静
Hey, man, I can be quiet.
只要你...要求
You can just... ask.
人造骨骼校准未完成
Synthetic calibration incomplete.
原地待命 很快回来
Stand by. I'll be back.
好了 女士
Here you go, ma'am.
我要一杯黑咖啡 不加糖
Yeah, give me a black coffee, no sugar.
没问题 沃格尔探员
You got it, Detective Vogel.
沃格尔警官 很高兴再见到您
Officer Vogel, it's good to see you again.
你是谁
Who are you?
这种人造人好几年都没见过了
Haven't seen one of those synthetics for years.
妙极
It's perfect.
两个垃圾堆里捡来的警察
Two cops from the scrap heap.
比我想得更可悲啊
This is gonna be more pathetic than I thought.
这些就是取代我的那款
Those are the models that replaced me.
真吓人
Intimidating.
去注册 准备走了
Go register so we can get moving.
DRN注册完毕
DRN registration complete.
嘿 机器人
Hey, bot.
别把我们给咬了
Don't snap on us, now.
长官 沃格尔探员被绑架了
Sir, Detective Vogel's been abducted.
马尔多纳多希望你来调查
Maldonado wants you on it.
他的MX被销毁了
His MX was destroyed.
残余的数据只有这些
This is all we could get off it.
从面具来判断
Based on the masks,
这跟那次武装抢劫是同一伙人
these are the same guys from the armed robbery.
嫌疑人从郡医院带来了吗
Suspect back from County?
你的人杀了我们四个警卫
Your gang kills four security guards.
现在又抓了个警察
Now you've taken a cop.
他在哪
Where is he?
他们抓他是因为你在我们手上吗
Did they take him 'cause we have you?
你知道这是什么吗
You know what this is?
是你的登记文件
It's your booking file.
记录着我们抓到你时你的状况
It describes the condition you were in when we got you.
那
Now...
你们拿走可编程DNA做什么
What are you doing with programmable DNA?
迈克隆红有什么用途
What's the Myklon Red for?
哦 看哪 嫌犯眼睛上方有一条抓痕
Oh, look, suspect has a scratch above his eye.
不知道怎么弄的
I have no idea how he got that.
添加到文件里 可能还要添加"臼齿失踪"
Better add it, and get ready to write down "missing molar".
还有别的办法 警探
There are other ways, Detective.
是我在审问这人 不是你 明白
I'm questioning this man, okay, not you.
那么
Now...
人造骨骼失灵 需要校准
Synthetic fail. Calibration required.
人造骨骼...
Synthetic fa...
枪是你自己开的
You shot yourself.
也许今早比较混乱
Perhaps it was a bit crazy this morning,
所以郡里的医生可能没看出来
maybe the doctors at County even missed it,
但是 根据你中的子弹的轨迹
but the trajectory of the bullet that hit you,
还有你肌肉烧伤的形状
the burn marks on your flesh--
基本上可以确定
basically there's no chance
子弹不会来自别人的手枪
that you were hit by a bullet from any gun but your own.
真的吗
Is that true?
你不了解我在为谁卖命
You don't know the people I work for.
相信我 我了解
Trust me, I do.
我必须想尽一切办法离开他们
I needed to get away from them any way I could,
因为谁都无法逃走
because there's no getting away from them.
听着 我们能帮你
Look, we can help you,
可以保证你安全 但你必须给我们信息
we can keep you safe, but you need to give us information.
不 我到哪里都不安全 包括这里
No, I'm not safe anywhere, not even here.
我们会把你安置在有守卫的安全地点
We'll put you in a secure location under guard.
谁都找不到你 但你必须先坦白
No one will find you, but you need to talk.
那地方一定要非常安全
I need to be somewhere safe.
沃格尔探员在哪
Then, where's Detective Vogel?
地址是什么
What's the address?
格兰德街325号 6号公寓
325 Grand, Apartment 6.
这可能不需要我多说
Not that you need me to tell you this,
但你刚刚侵犯了那人的人权
but you just violated the crap out of that guy's civil rights.
真神奇 我的这个人造人心肠还挺软
Fantastic, I get the synthetic with the bleeding heart.
听着 我不管你的程序是什么
Look, I don't care what you're programmed to do.
你要是敢上报这件事 我就把你推下楼
You report what happened in there and you'll find yourself bouncing down the 604.
探长 如果我上报任何事
Detective, if I'm going to report anything,
都是因为我认为此事应该上报
it is because I decided it needed to be reported.
我不舒服
I feel sick.
我要去厕所
I need a toilet.
你还好吗
You all right?
我没事
I'll be fine.
停
Stop.
潜在爆炸装置
Potential explosive device.
人类退后
Humans back.
撤空大楼
Evacuate the building.
DRN 停止前进 停止前进
DRN, halt advancement, halt advancement.
探长
Detective.
这是什么
What is it?
这不是炸弹
It's not a bomb.
这线通往另一处
That trip wire leads somewhere.
我带你去
I'll lead you in?
我不建议如此 长官
I do not advise that, sir.
我们走
Let's go.
沃格尔
Vogel.
救命
Help!
冷静
Stay calm.
肯尼思 救我
Kennex, help me!
救我
Help!
做点什么
Do something!
防弹玻璃
Bulletproof glass.
边缘被焊上了
It's welded shut.
我是帕特尔
Patel speaking.
帕特尔 你在哪
Patel, where are you?
去安全屋的路上
En route to the safe house.
犯人在车里
We have the perp in the car.
好 赶紧掉头 这一切都是陷阱
Okay, turn around... this whole thing's a setup.
帕特尔 帕特尔
Patel, Patel.
不 不
No, no, no, no...
帕特尔队长和两名警察被杀
Sergeant Patel and two other officers were killed,
三个MX被摧毁 嫌疑人也逃跑了
three MXs were destroyed, and the suspect escaped.
是时候了
It's about time.
我很遗憾
I'm sorry.
法医鉴定太慢了
Morgue lab is too slow.
找个试验箱 取点他的血样 带给鲁迪分析一下
Get a lab box, take a sample of his blood, and send it to Rudy for analysis.
不需要试验箱
Don't need a lab box.
我刚下载了资料
I just downloaded the information.
鲁迪现在应该有数据了
Rudy should have the data now.
为什么是他
Why him?
为什么攻击沃格尔
Why target Vogel?
搜索沃格尔接手的案件
Scan every case Vogel was on.
任何有关生物技术 科学 医药 DNA的案件
Any connection to biotech, science, medicine, DNA.
我都要看
I want to see it.
我不知道这是为什么
I don't know if this is anything,
但是他其中一个案件丢失了
but one of his files is missing.
案卷6663
Case file number 6663.
从内部资料丢失的
It's gone from all internal records.
等一下 沃格尔探员今早跟我说
Wait a minute, Detective Vogel told me this morning
他不能用他的终端
that he couldn't get access to his terminal.
也许是带走他的人删掉了文件
Maybe whoever took him was deleting the file.
他们进入了整个系统
They got into the whole system.
他们是谁
Who is they?
看看楼下的人谁能把文件找回来
See if anyone downstairs can get that file back.
我就去
On my way.
你刚说的话...
The way you said that...
说明你已经有怀疑的人了
you're thinking someone specific is behind this.
是谁
Who?
我需要你帮忙时候 我会说的
When I want your help, I'll ask for it.
你知道你问题是什么吗
You know what your problem is?
我一天中最喜欢的是
Always my favorite part of the day:
让一个人造人告诉我 我有什么问题
a synthetic telling me what my problem is.
又是这个词
There's that word again.
你的问题是 你不了解你自己
Your problem is, you don't know yourself.
你不信任任何人
You don't trust anyone.
这是我的问题吗
Is that my problem?
伙计 我不是在责怪你
And, man, I don't blame you.
毕竟你经历了这么多
After all you've been through,
如果我是你 我也不会了解我自己
if I were like you, I wouldn't know myself either.
好吧 第一 别再说"伙计"
Okay, firstly stop saying "Man."
第二 你不像我
Secondly you're not like me.
但我也不像他们
And I'm not like them.
MX系列是基于逻辑判断和遵循规则的模型
MX units are logic-based and rule-oriented.
他们没有自由意志
They have no true free will
他们被设计成没有感觉
and they are designed to feel nothing.
我不能说我是生出来的
Now, I can't say that I was born,
我不能说我是在子宫里孕育或者拥有童年
I can't say I grew in a womb or had a childhood,
但我被做设计为拥有情感 我也确实有
but I was made to feel and I do
和你一样多
as much as you.
我读了你写的东西
I read what you wrote:
如果MX当初没有丢下你去救其他人
that if an MX hadn't left you behind to save some others,
你的搭档可能成功躲开那次伏击
your partner might have made it out of that ambush alive,
这部分可能是真的
and that part may be true,
但是我读了整个报告
but I read the whole report.
那时伏击已经开始
By the time the ambush had begun,
已经来不及了 是你硬带他们去
it was already too late and it was you who led them in,
你可以责怪MX 也可以责怪你自己
so you can blame an MX or you can blame yourself.
好吧
Okay,
- 我和MX43不一样 - 你现在很显然出故障了
- I am nothing like an MX-43. - You're obviously malfunctioning right now.
- 你何不花几秒重启一下 - 不要这样跟我说话
- Why don't you just take a second to reboot yourself? - Do not talk to me that way.
- 就算有人出故障了 也是你肯尼思 - 你知道我将停止干什么
- If anyone is malfunctioning, it is you, Kennex. - You know what I'm gonna stop doing?
我将停止和一片硅胶和碳纤维争论
I'm gonna stop arguing with a piece of silicon and carbon fiber.
肯尼思
Kennex.
是鲁迪
It's Rudy.
警察局的所有警察被强制要求注射
All police in the department are required to have mandatory inoculation
警局实验室研发的疫苗 只对警官
designed in police labs for officers only.
这本来是为了保护警察的安全
Those inoculations are meant to keep cops safe.
免受生物战 毒气 致病菌等伤害
Protects against biowarfare, gases, pathogens, et cetera.
我们在沃格尔的血样里发现迈克隆红
We found Myklon Red in Vogel's blood,
结合了可编程DNA
combined with programmable DNA.
这样就直接攻击了疫苗
It targets the inoculation directly.
就像一次感染了上百种不同的疾病
It's like getting a hundred different diseases at once.
免疫系统变得狂躁
The immune system goes berserk.
你在说什么鲁迪
What are you saying, Rudy?
这就是为什么他的身体起那种反映
That's why his body reacted in the way that it did.
这就是为什么他死了
That's why he died.
我认为沃格尔探员是个试验体
I believe Detective Vogel was a test subject.
我们要对付的人...
Whoever we're up against...
他们目标是警察
They're targeting cops.
你去哪
Where are you going?
我不允许你这么做
I cannot allow you to do this.
这离上次才没多久
It's far too soon.
这是我的事 好吗
Look, this isn't about me, okay?
有人想杀光警察
Someone is killing police officers,
找到他们的唯一方法
and the only way we're gonna find them
就是我能记起更多参与这事的人
is if I remember more about the people who are doing it.
约翰 这不安全
John, it's not safe for you.
你就这么做 现在就做
You do this and you do it now.
他们早就等着我们送上门了 约翰
They were ready for us, John.
反联组织怎么知道我们要来
How did Insyndicate know we were coming?
他们怎么知道的 怎么...
How did they know? How'd they...?
回来 你个死机器人
Hey, come back here! You're damn rob...!
对不起
I am so sorry.
我告诉他这太危险了
I told him it was too dangerous.
你用了我的定位芯片
You used my locator chip.
马尔多纳多让我盯着你
Maldonado wanted me to keep an eye on you.
好吧
Okay.
能有一个软心肠的搭档 你很幸运
You're lucky you got the partner with the bleeding heart.
你在下面的时候看见了什么
What did you see... when you were under?
我看见我亲近的人
I saw someone who was close to me.
那个人 我现在才意识到不应该相信她的
Someone who, I realize now, that I should never have trusted.
我想说 虽然我不确定那是否是真的 但是...
I want to say I... I'm not even sure it's real, but...
但是是真的
But it was.
是谁呢 约翰
Who was it, John?
我前女友
It was my ex-girlfriend.
当我从昏迷中醒过来的时候 她已经消失了
When I came out of my coma, she had disappeared.
现在我知道原因了
Now I know why.
人造骨骼失灵
Synthetic fail.
需要校准
Calibration required.
人造骨骼失灵 需要校准
Synthetic fail. Calibration required.
我能解决这个问题
I've got a fix for that.
解决什么
What?
是不是有时会吱嘎作响
It gets creaky sometimes?
我有办法解决这个问题
I've got a fix for that.
用橄榄油
Olive oil.
橄榄油
Olive oil?
没错 你把橄榄油倒在关节的地方
Yeah, man. You put it right on the joint.
橄榄油
Olive oil?
你会感激我的
You'll thank me.
我想我...
I suppose I, uh...
我应该感谢你救了我
I should acknowledge the fact that you saved my life.
不用谢
No need.
我这么做只因为你是我唯一的机会
I only did it because you're my one ticket.
没有你 我就没法在这里
Without you, I'm off the force.
你该庆幸我太想当警察了
You're lucky I want to be a cop so bad.
你不像他们 那些MX机器人
You're not like them, the MXs.
我不知道为什么 但你就不像他们
I don't know why, but you're not.
你这应该是在表扬我吧
I should take that as a compliment.
没错
You should.
MX系列建立在一阶谓词演算之上
The MX series is based on first order predicate calculus.
MX没有知觉 你也可以说他们没有灵魂
MXs have no intuition, or as you might say, no soul.
对他们来说 经验 记忆都只是记录好的数据
For them, experience, memory is just recorded data.
我这个系列被设计用来归纳总结
My series is designed to draw conclusions,
做出推论
make inferences.
答案是沃格尔 对吧
The answer is Vogel, right?
谁在针对他 好处又是什么
Who was targeting him, what was the payback for?
是啊
Yeah.
我们唯一证人就是沃格尔的MX
And the only witness we have is Vogel's MX,
但在他们带走沃格尔的时候已经粉身碎骨了
Who was blown apart when they took Vogel.
是啊 鲁迪说他的神经网络已经彻底瘫痪了
Yeah, Ru-Rudy said his neural net was completely fried.
别的MX对此毫无办法
Worthless to another MX,
他们无法联系证据 理解证据
who wouldn't be able to-to put it together, to make sense of it,
但你可以建立起那些联系
but you could make those connections.
如果我们传送记忆
If we transferred the memory,
把沃格尔的MX残存的记忆传送给你
or whatever's left of the memory from Vogel's MX to you,
你就能够建立起连接
you could make the connection.
值得一试 探长
It's worth a shot, Detective.
买单啦
Check, please!
我在它的短时记忆中
I'm in its short-term memory now.
原地待命 很快回来
Stand by. I'll be back.
咖啡...糖...
...coffee... sugar.
沃格尔探员
Officer Vogel.
很高兴再次见到您
It's good to see you again.
几年前 你把一些不属于你的东西
A few years ago, you logged something into evidence
记录成证据
that doesn't belong to you.
你可能还记得6663号案件吧
You may remember it as case number 6663.
不记得了
No?
你们辖区的人一直很贴心地保管着它
Well, your precinct has been kind enough to hold it in evidence,
但今晚 我们要把它拿回来
but tonight, we're gonna get it back,
你会帮我们搞定
and you're gonna help us do it.
我们有他们要的东西
We've got something they want.
头儿 我们需要启动一级防范措施
Captain, we need to go into lockdown.
怎么了
What's going on?
他们今晚要攻击我们
They're hitting us tonight.
他们要在物证室找什么东西
They're after something in the evidence room!
打开吧 干掉所有MX
Light it up, take out the MXs.
反联组织的人在屋顶上
The Insyndicates are on the roof!
快啊 赶紧的 快快
Come on, now. Go, go, go, go, go!
疏散大楼
Evacuate building.
为什么他们倒下了而你没有
Why are they shutting down and not you?
他们跟我在不同的频率上
They run on a different frequency than mine.
有时候更先进的科技不一定更好
Sometimes newer technology isn't better.
走吧
Come on.
打开阀门
Open the valves.
我们要自己动手一个一个检查
We got to go through every piece by hand.
我们都不知道要找什么呢
We don't even know what we're looking for.
我们知道它在这
We know it's here.
而且我们知道它肯定很重要
And we know it's valuable because they were willing
因为他们为了它杀了不少警察
to kill a lot of cops to get it.
肯定有某种方法能够让被消除的证据恢复
There must be some way to restore those evidence files that were wiped.
我在努力了
I've been trying,
但破坏太彻底了
but the sabotage was extremely thorough.
我会继续努力
I'll keep trying.
谢啦 老兄
Thanks, man.
起来
Rise...
又一个好了
and be counted.
别惹麻烦
Stay out of trouble.
你爸爸肯定会喜欢这个地方
Your father would have loved this place.
哦 我等不及要回到你的身边了
Oh, I can't wait to get back to you.
我知道我还得再等一个星期
I know I have to wait a week,
但是我真的很希望你能在这里陪着我
but what I really wish is that you were here with me.
我们会找到她的 约翰
We're gonna find her, John.
要是你没有回来...
If you hadn't come back...
你救了很多人的命
You saved a lot of lives.
谢谢
Thanks.
谢谢你的坚持
Thanks for insisting.
是你申请的允许多利安服役的授权令
You put in the rec order... for Dorian.
我检查了他的记录
I checked out his record.
大部分被修改过 但我看见是你提出让我去找他的申请
It's mostly redacted, but I saw that it was you who put in the request for me to get him.
为什么
Why?
DRN对你有好处
The DRN is good for you.
桑德拉
Sandra...
你没回答我问题呢
you didn't answer my question.
为什么是多利安
Why Dorian?
因为他很特殊
'Cause he's special.
跟你一样与众不同
Just like you.
等下在点名时见
See you at roll call.
我猜你又需要安静模式了 探长
I assume you want quiet mode, Detective?
没必要了
Not necessarily.
叫我约翰吧
Call me John.
呼出颗粒物检测
文件访问用户名
姓名: 皮特 沃格尔
职位: 探员
拒绝访问
32302号终端下线
迈克隆红
对象识别
约翰 肯尼思
无法识别危险
分析无结果
拘禁中
特雷弗 詹恩斯
遗传标记吻合
删除 保存